嗯。新疆维吾尔自治区新疆生产建设兵团，二零二零年初中学业水平考试英语试卷听力部分，请大家做好准备。听力测试现在开始。第一大题，听力。
a. 1. I can play the guitar and I want to join the music club
听音选图。句子理解：根据听到的句子内容，选择正确的图。图片。每小题读两遍。
2. Allen has a soccer ball.
Allen likes playing sports
3. Bad luck.
I lost my key and I cannot open the door
4. that giraffe is so beautiful
5. Linda usually gets up at 8 in the morning
情景反映。听句子，选择正确的应答。每小题读两遍。
6. Who's that girl?
7. Is the radio station far from here?
8. Adment, you look cool with the
9. are you so happy today?
10. Hi, team.
How's everything going?
c. 11. Eric takes after his father.
对话理解。听对话及问题，选择正确的答案。每组对话读两遍。
Yes, they're both tall and outgoing c.
12. The book Journey to the West is so interesting, isn't it?
13. book Journey to the West is so interesting, isn't it?
14. The book Journey to the West isn't it?
Where are the two speakers?
Sir, what would you like?
17. I'd 18.
black one is my favorite.
I'll take it.
Which t -shirt will the man buy?
Which t will the man buy?
t -shirt will buy?
Which t will the Which t -shirt will the man buy?
短文理解。听短文，选择正确的答案。短文读两遍。
Which t will 25.
Which t 26.
Which t -shirt will the man
27. Which t -shirt will 28.
t -shirt will the buy?
听力测试到此结束。